[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These are the four types of graffiti styles.", "correct_answer": "Tagging, hate, gang, and generic", "incorrect_answers": ["Sentence, quote, movie, and stylish", "Love, fame, simultaneous and generic", "Dusty, reddish, round, and square"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these salads has the lowest amount of carbohydrates and sugar?", "correct_answer": "Burger King Fire-Grilled Chicken Caesar Salad", "incorrect_answers": ["Wendys Chicken BLT Salad", "Arbys Market Fresh Santa Fe Salad", "Taco Bell Fiesta Taco Salad"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which US state has been nicknamed The First State, The Small Wonder, Blue Hen State, and The Diamond State?", "correct_answer": "Delaware", "incorrect_answers": ["Pennsylvania", "Virginia", "New York"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the incubation period for turtle-dove eggs?", "correct_answer": "12-14 days", "incorrect_answers": ["7 weeks", "17-25 days", "1 month"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the little green boards in the computer called?", "correct_answer": "daughter cards", "incorrect_answers": ["son boards", "father cards", "motherboards"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the cat that belonged to Topper in Thorne Smiths fiction?", "correct_answer": "Scallops", "incorrect_answers": ["Brutus", "Pestilence", "Alexander"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor portrayed agent James Bond in the 1964 movie Goldfinger?", "correct_answer": "Sean Connery", "incorrect_answers": ["Timothy Dalton", "Roger Moore", "George Lazenby"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What singer and actress starred in the 1990 dramedy movie Mermaids?", "correct_answer": "Cher", "incorrect_answers": ["Vanessa Williams", "Madonna", "Dolly Parton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During what geological period did the earliest vascular plants evolve?", "correct_answer": "Silurian", "incorrect_answers": ["Devonian", "Cretaceous", "Cambrian"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Facing the Giants, Grant Taylors car battery dies every time on his way home from work.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Female Tomato Frogs are larger than male Tomato Frogs.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who wrote and performed the 1997 hit song Angels?", "correct_answer": "Robbie Williams", "incorrect_answers": ["Sting", "George Michael", "Elton John"]}]